<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>poliastro - articles</title><link href="http://poliastro.github.io/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="http://poliastro.github.io/feeds/articles.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>http://poliastro.github.io/</id><updated>2018-02-22T12:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>Join poliastro thanks to Google Summer of Code!</title><link href="http://poliastro.github.io/2018/02/22/2018-02-22-join-poliastro-google-summer-of-code/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2018-02-22T12:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2018-02-22T12:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>Juan Luis Cano Rodríguez</name></author><id>tag:poliastro.github.io,2018-02-22:2018/02/22/2018-02-22-join-poliastro-google-summer-of-code/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;We are glad to announce that &lt;strong&gt;poliastro&lt;/strong&gt; will accept student applications during Google Summer of Code this year, thanks to the umbrella organization OpenAstronomy! 🚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the newcomers, poliastro is a pure Python library that allows you to easily simulate and visualize interplanetary orbits in an interactive way, &lt;a href="http://docs.poliastro.space/en/v0.8.0/index.html#success-stories"&gt;used by people from all around the world&lt;/a&gt;. Sounds interesting? Read on!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;What is Google Summer of Code?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Google Summer of Code&lt;/strong&gt; (from now on, &lt;strong&gt;GSOC&lt;/strong&gt;) is, according to &lt;a href="https://summerofcode.withgoogle.com/"&gt;its own website&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a global program focused on bringing more student developers into open source software development. Students work with an open source organization on a 3 month programming project during their break from school.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt="Google Summer of Code" src="https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/1/1e/GSoC.png"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GSOC is the inspiration for the Summer of Code in Space (SOCIS), a similar program organized by the European Space Agency in which &lt;a href="http://blog.poliastro.space/2017/09/15/2017-09-15-poliastro-070-released-ready-pycones/"&gt;we also participated last year&lt;/a&gt;, with …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="GSOC"></category><category term="Google"></category><category term="poliastro"></category><category term="students"></category></entry><entry><title>poliastro 0.7.0 released and ready for PyConES!</title><link href="http://poliastro.github.io/2017/09/15/2017-09-15-poliastro-070-released-ready-pycones/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-09-15T11:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2017-09-15T11:00:00+02:00</updated><author><name>Juan Luis Cano Rodríguez</name></author><id>tag:poliastro.github.io,2017-09-15:2017/09/15/2017-09-15-poliastro-070-released-ready-pycones/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;It fills us with astronomical joy to announce the release of &lt;strong&gt;poliastro 0.7.0&lt;/strong&gt;! 🚀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the newcomers, poliastro is a pure Python library that allows you to simulate and analyze interplanetary orbits in a Jupyter notebook in an interactive and easy way, &lt;a href="http://docs.poliastro.space/en/v0.7.0/index.html#success-stories"&gt;used by people from all around the world&lt;/a&gt;. Sounds interesting? Read on!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This release is the biggest one since the creation of the project in terms of code changes and new features, and on behalf of the poliastro development team I would like to deeply thank the European Space Agency for the SOCIS grant that made it possible. Besides, I would like to officially welcome Antonio Hidalgo to the team, since in reward for his amazing work during SOCIS he gained write access to the repository. ¡Bienvenido Antonio!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, the easiest way to get poliastro in …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="SOCIS"></category><category term="poliastro"></category><category term="releases"></category><category term="PyConES"></category></entry></feed>